[Music]
happy birthday to
you Thank you guys for the
greetings so My wish is um good
health for everybody ah espcially to
my family especially to my son who was
hospitalized recently Our time in the
hospital even though we have HMO but because it is
big because the help of fwd because
we have an allowance that we got This is
the hospital cash benefit your policy
Yes Actually hm you are only 2 King he is in the
room we made room 2
he is at 28 per day so that's the fwd
allowance that also helps him to
cover that and then when we checked out there was a
follow up what a checkup
my son was prescribed pred sims
that's what I used to buy
vitamins So how did you file the claim
CL It was very easy when I opened the
application I just went to the ah
manager policy Then there you submit
you just get the requirements
like medical certificate ah needed
there then statement of account then there
you just pick Then you also put in
what you Of course the bank information
Your preferred bank where
the claim will go  So there you have it,
I got it within 2 days, it's just that
fast, unlike others, do you still have to talk to
a financial advisor before you can
claim or do you go to the
site where you claim it yourself? So did
you use all of that? Of course, there's a reason for
that, I put it in UM in
our funds. Where is what
enjoyable um calls money you keep aside for the
quality of your life? That's the beauty of
having an insurance because
there is this bill. You need to pass it away and
get benefits from it. So
we call that giving benefits.
Your business is yours. Hopefully, it's
right. Or you can't sell your property
or maybe it's part of Filipino culture. Is it a
loan? Family or I
know what's for sale? Rush, that's it, isn't it?
I sold my iPhone 16.
I'm looking forward to
my investment maturing so that when it makes
money, I'll use the other part
for business or retirement,
then I'll put the rest in there so that
my policies are still active. So it's not just
about you.  know claiming because
you got sick or um you passed away that
you can claim from from it a room a life
insurance You can also claim a lot
from insurance It depends on what the
insurance
[Music]
plan Of course you want your phone to be
tied to you It's worth the fee
you can enjoy it so with insurance it
should be That's also the same you have a sense of comfort
and security so I'll also Actually it's
simple um the person I Can Trust
really likes to bike so same
passion point as the financial advisor
Okay so he gave me a tip that
of course we do these activities
So it should be so you have a sense of
security and you know you have a sense of
p of my safety you and peace of mind very
hands on I like what you're helping
me figure out What are the
steps I need to do to
achieve what I want co
convenience and accessibility because
That's when you have issues it
seems easy for me to manage it By
Myself because it's on the app because I bought
my insurance when I was single then
also on the app that I changed
my beneficiary  My wife
just uploaded the marriage contract and
then the next day
fwd emailed me. I changed the ad so
I'm a beneficiary and then when you have a baby
you can also add a
beneficiary using the omni app
just clicks. We got life insurance in
December last year and then this year
I got Trin right away. Is
life insurance really real? It's really
helpful. It's
easy and legit. It's 100 percent. What else do
customers receive? When we are
customers, we
really put a lot of value in it. You know,
building a relationship with our
advisors and also with our customers. So
we do a lot of effort strengthening
that relationship. When
our customers achieve specific milestones, we celebrate with them,
for example, for your birthday.
We want to make sure that
we have a gift for you. That's right. And
if you're done paying
the premium on your policy, we're going to be
helping you together with your advisor.
what's next so we send
communications to help you grow
your understanding on finances
We try as much as we can Uh to be with
our customers life stages a nga and
milestone be with them um helping them
and celebrate the thank you Thank you St
fwd because I didn't really spend
ah
ah money I maximized the life
insurance I bought for my son
That's all I can say to fwd happing
happy very reassuring to me that
I'm in the middle of payment of
policies that I know that there is certainty
and security for fw that she will fulfill her
promises I feel like secured
and very thankful for the flexibility that
I experience with fwd when
people understand the um benefits of having
insurance can celebrate Are they
really good with the tagline celebrate
live Yes very Yes because that's the reality
of life e ba only So you have to
celebrate it Otherwise you should
insure yourself
now us if that now
[Music]
Then ah